# **Kaleb Kloppe**

#### ABOUT

Kaleb Kloppe combines five years of experience in design and photography with education in psychology and advertising to create and execute compelling experiences that align with business goals. He is seeking a position in UI and UX design.

#### PORTFOLIO

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### 2019-PRESENT

#### DIGITAL DESIGNER

MobileFuse

Translated client briefs into live ad units. Provided Art Direction to junior team members. Managed creative QA testing. In a 12-month period, utilized visual and web design expertise to deliver 108 unique rich media ads for mobile users.

## 2015-2016 VISUAL DESIGNER

Stirista

Created user interfaces for three web applications, designed dozens of pieces of print and digital collateral, and managed the company's Wordpress website. Following the 2015 redesign of Stirista's online onboarding process, new user signups increased 288% month-over-month.

## 2013-2014 PHOTOGRAPHER

Freelance

Provided portrait and product photography to dozens of private clients. Published two photos in GM High Tech Performance Magazine and Nfit Magazine.

#### **EDUCATION**

2017–2019 C

#### CONTINUING EDUCATION — GRAPHIC DESIGN

Rhode Island School of Design

## 2016-2018 MASTER OF SCIENCE — ADVERTISING

**Boston University** 

## 2011-2014 BACHELOR OF ARTS — POLITICAL SCIENCE AND PSYCHOLOGY

University of Texas at San Antonio

#### ADDRESS

680 E Basse Rd, Apt 406 San Antonio, Tx 78209

#### CONTACT

kmkloppe@gmail.com 210-854-2187

#### SKILLS

## DESIGN

HTML + CSS + JS
Print + Digital Design
UI + UX Design
Rapid Prototyping
Wireframing

## **PHOTOGRAPHY**

Portraiture Photoshop Lightroom

#### Video

Cinematography Video Editing Color Grading